Now, our next speaker is the uh is the
uh founder and CEO of a little company
called Tessle. Uh 18-month old company.
Um GIO previously is he's a serial
founder. He he he founded Blaze, which
was acquired. He founded Sneak, a
massively successful developer security
uh company and organization that
actually when we think about it, a lot
of the challenges that that had in and
around moving the the thought process,
moving the moving the mindset of people
to a developer security path is actually
very similar to how we're thinking today
about A&E development. And now we're
going to talk about how AI can be done
collaboratively. So please give it up
for our first keynote speaker, Guy
Pjani.
>> [applause]
[music]
>> Hello everyone. Uh, welcome to the first
inerson and native DevCon. Uh, love in
person events, you know, like I think
you you you convey things virtually. I
consume things virtually, but nothing
beats, you know, talking to people and
engaging with them. And I hope you're
all feeling that way. So, thanks for
shipping in, especially in the rain here
in New York. and uh uh and I hope you
you enjoy the event and I look forward
to meeting and learning from many of
you. Uh I am Gapari or I am the
founder and CEO of TESL. Uh and I'm here
to talk about specdriven development's
growth uh from kind of single player to
really how do you use it in a team and
how do you think about ecosystems? Um
let me set the stage first. So hopefully
we're all aligned that AI is
transforming software development. It's
not a little hiccup. It's not a little
change. It's something that is
substantial that is happening and we've
seen a bunch of evolution already. We've
had two kind of waves of what I think of
as AI augmented software development uh
with tools that were pioneered by
copilot and cursor that autocomplete
things better you know that that helped
a lot that build in chat and allow you
to talk to your code and understand
things that cursor pioneered and then we
uh in this last sort of especially 6
months maybe 12 we've seen the rise of
more true AI native which I think of
them as more AI native dev tools because
they're more about delegation they're
more uh ask the agent to do a thing for
you and then interact with it. So, it's
a it's a much more substantial change
for us and there's a lot to learn. And
while all of these tools are are
valuable in their own right, they've all
kind of consolidated towards this
agentic behavior. Uh and I think it's
pretty clear that that is the future.
So, I'll focus on where is that taking
us? You know, how do we make this
agentic development work?
So, the reality today is that agents are
are super powerful, uh, but they're
massively unreliable, right? They're
sort of sometimes spooky, sometimes
kooky. You know, they're they're uh
they're they're amazing and they do
these things that astound you, but then
they just make these foolish mistakes.
Um, they're also very untrustworthy.
They'll tell you something is done when
it isn't really. They will break things
along the way as they, you know, you ask
them to build a feature, they'll burn
down the house to to get it done. Uh,
and so they're very powerful, uh, but
they're kind of hard to use. Um, and
this creates this capability reliability
gap, you know, and you see studies like
this one from meter where they they
assess, you know, how how much do
developers think AI tools will make them
better. And you see this is the bar at
the left and people developers, well, I
think it's going to make me faster. I'll
complete something faster. And then they
observe how long it actually takes them
to do it. And it turns out it actually
was slower. There's a lot of caveats, a
lot of flaws in this study and in any of
the others. It's a very complex area,
but I think everybody relates to the
fact that it's not easy to turn this
power into improved productivity into
something that actually works.
And and so what do we do about it? Well,
what we can't do about it is say, you
know, bury your head in the sand like
let's not use agents is tempting. And,
you know, a good number of people,
probably none in this room are uh are
saying that. Uh but you know it's
clearly shortsighted. I mean this is a
technology that's too powerful that uh
to to kind of ignore or think it would
fade away. It's here. It's going to
shape our development. And we need to
think about how do we embrace it? Not
how do we ignore it? And so the real
question is how do we help agents? How
do we help agents succeed and close this
capability reliability gap?
Let's look a little bit at a at a
history of attempting to do so. You
know, this is uh our quest for silver
bullets that would make LLMs work uh the
way we want, right? And a bit of a loose
timeline. We start off with, you know,
this is us as the industry thinking
about fine-tuning. Hey, we're going to
tell the LLM, here are like tens,
hundreds, maybe thousands of examples of
how I like to code, how you code in my
environment on it, and the LLM's weights
will magically adapt uh and work like
that. And it turns out that this works
very well for brand new skills, for
cases in which you're teaching the LLM
to do something that it didn't know
before. But if it already has opinions,
if it already knows how to code, it's
very hard to sway it. It's kind of like
people, you know, we if if can't teach
an old dog new tricks, right? It's hard
to sway someone will behave. And so
fine-tuning is useful, but it's not a
silver bullet. And in fact, in many
cases, uh it is it is hard to to really
have it shine.
The second kind of wave of technology of
this will solve our problems was was
rag. It's like I will take my prompt and
I will put it into this magical kind of
embedding algorithms and vector
databases will pull out the right
context that I need everything precisely
that I need to know to be able to
address this problem. And again rag very
powerful when you have your own keywords
and terminology and things like that but
uh context gathering is more complicated
than that. uh there's there's a lot of
subtlety often time things that are not
in your prompt they're not in that
initial path and so it remained a useful
tool but was deemed not uh not a silver
bullet
um the next kind of this will save us
all was the world of big context you
know what we don't need to worry about
all this stuff you know we've got like
million token 2 million token context
windows we'll just tell it everything uh
and it will figure it out it'll just
sort of know what to do and it turns out
you know like I often get uh the like
through my career I've gotten the often
times the guidance that says if you have
10 smart things to say and you say all
of them each of them will get less
attention than if you said three of them
uh and and I still struggle to not say
everything I think but uh it but it's
true you know if you say fewer things
each of them gets more attention and
NLMs are the same they if you if you
give it more information in its context
each of these bits would get less
attention it would be less focused and
we'll show a little bit of that in a sec
and so we get into modern world uh and
we have these two additional tools. One
is agentic search. You know what? Let's
delegate the actual problem of context
creation to the agent. Let's give it
tools to find the information. That's
what we do as humans. We go, we Google,
we look at files, we uh we do that work.
And that is useful, but again, it's
useful when it's constrained. If you
tell someone just just go find, you
know, the information about anything,
it'll take time to find it. It'll take
uh you might find the wrong information.
uh and you know it's a in it's both
inefficient and unbounded and you can
get down rabbit holes that really kind
of make things worse and so it's a very
very powerful tool. We'll refer to it
back again but again it didn't just
solve the problem because there's
another piece that we need on top of
that and that is context engineering and
that's the sort of the state of affairs
today which is you actually have to give
up on the magic solutions and think
about what do you want to tell the
agent? what information does the agent
need to succeed? And I love uh this is
uh Toby, the uh founder and CEO of
Shopify. He's a very serial guy, super
smart guy, and he was on the podcast uh
uh a couple of months ago. And I like
his quotes here, which is I like the
term context engineering because I think
the fundamental skill of using AI well
is to be able to, and this is the key
word, a state of problem with enough
context in such a way that without any
additional pieces of information, the
task is plausibly solvable. I love that
it's this notion of like let it lean
into intelligence but don't assume mind
readading you know like tell it what it
needs to know so that it can succeed.
So context engineering in my mind and I
might be biased is basically the same as
specs. You know this is about we just
had this long conversation about you
know should we call something spec or
context. uh it doesn't really matter
like for me it is about getting out of
your head and out of your knowledge
getting the the nuggets of knowledge
that you need to uh give the agent to
succeed and so I'm going to use the term
context and specs interchangeably
throughout this talk that's the way I
see the world
so I'm going to go into that sort of
single multi-ecosystem player but before
that I want to remind us that you can't
optimize what you can't measure this is
a known phrase in the world of software
development but really mostly you hear
it about ops because in ops we are
familiar with these systems that
sometimes behave well and sometimes
don't right the the servers sometimes
work sometimes don't sometimes they
crash and so we have to measure them so
we know what's happening so we can
optimize it now we have the same
statistical behavior in our development
you know we have these statistical
creatures agents they build stuff
sometimes they work sometimes they don't
and that means two things one we need to
leave the notion of agents can
absolutely do this or cannot absolutely
and embrace a statistical number around
their success uccess rate and two is we
have to measure that we have to think
about how do we evaluate how do we
assess success and I'll try to give some
data to back some of my statements in
this talk
so now we'll actually get to the thing
that is on the title which is let's talk
about uh single player how do you do
context engineering in a single player
context so um just to demonstrate a
little bit the the base this is a a um a
little sample to-do application with a
Jurassic theme that I worked very hard
on uh to just sort of demonstrate
And the base context that an agent has
is your project. Here I'm asking the
agent to add an edit button to each of
the to-do items in my list. And you'll
see the agent automatically go off and
read files in the project. It doesn't
read all of them. It's already doing a
gentic search to load uh some of that
content. Uh and then it would load that
code, understand that code, and uh
sorry, I'll just sort of pause here. uh
and um uh it it can load loads that code
and reads that into context. So, I
didn't need to tell it what the to-do
item is. I didn't need to tell it where
to put that button. It had enough
information in the code and this is the
base context that's important. However,
you'll notice for instance that it
created this blue edit button and that
doesn't fit my beautiful Jurassic theme.
Uh and it turns out that in the code
some information is not there. It
doesn't know that I want to stick to my
theme colors. And so let's tell it to do
that. So we can add explicit context
that doesn't rely on agentic search like
an agent MD file that says always stick
to the theme colors used British
spelling and it will go off and I will
ask the same action you know I will say
add an edit button and it will go off.
it'll do the same type of like dynamic
loading and uh maybe I'll sort of spare
us a moment here uh as we get to the end
you will see that it indeed created uh
the button with my beautiful theme
colors uh and and so this is this is 101
of context engineering at at the base
your project's context your project's
code is the agent's context how well
documented it is whether it is confusing
and has references to old data
structures that you have uh how um uh
reasonable are your file names all of
Those things help the agent load the
right files, but then there's going to
be some information that's not in the
code and you put in your explicit agents
MD, claude MD, cursor rules, local
context. You probably know much of this
already. The challenge is this is nice
when you want to tell it stick to the
theme colors, but typically you have a
lot more to say. You there's just a lot
that you want to tell it uh about how to
work in your environment, in your style.
And as we talked about before, if you
tell it 10 things, it's going to get,
you know, give each of them less
attention than if you told it three. Uh,
and so this is uh a problem. Before I
talk about how to solve it, let's maybe
back that claim that this is a problem
with some data. So to do that, we took a
little uh game, the team took a little
sort of dodge the blocks game uh that
that was vivecoded and asked uh the
asked an agent in this case Claude code.
Actually we tried three agents say add a
login to this like add sessionbacked
authentication so this game will be
behind the login. The other thing we did
is we created again with agents uh an
evaluation scorecard like how good is
the security of this thing that you've
just added just like a benchmark that
are standards today for good rubrics and
then we ran that in three different
modes. One is we ran the agents without
any context and we scored them. The
second is we put into the agents MD or
the equivalent uh the OASP the open web
application security project uh guidance
around authentication about 3 kilobytes
of data and the second is the longer 20
kilobytes of full security guidance that
includes the 3 kilobytes there's no word
that didn't exist in the second one and
indeed as we ran this we saw and I'm
just sort of you know uh this is no
surprise that without any guidance the
agent scored a 65 85% score and with the
guidance with the precise guidance it
got 85% score and if we told it more
things it got a lower score it got 81.
So this was good and it's already
validation. We need to know that even
though we expect this behavior now we
have a bit more confidence and there are
many examples of this but also we find
information that is maybe a bit
unexpected. For instance we ran this on
three different agents. We ran it on
claude on codeex and on cursor and what
you can see is they all fared about the
same mediocre results without any
guidance. There are many pitfalls that
you can have from a security perspective
when you add a login page, but there's a
big difference in how they handle the
deeper context. Claude shined when you
gave it precise instructions, but
dropped a fair bit uh when you gave it
the longer instruction. Codeex didn't do
as well in total, but dealt with the
longer context a lot more. And it's
interesting because it's not obvious to
people that not all agents listen the
same. You we told them the same words.
Some of these actually use the same
model behind them, but agents process
and make many decisions. And you know,
granted, there are 10 runs behind each
of these columns. So maybe there's also
not enough data for statistical
significance, but the results are
substantially different. And you have to
think not just about what is the
question you're asking and the
saturation, but also who are you asking
it of?
So, so we have this challenge. We want
to tell agents a lot of things and they
uh you know, we can't because it's going
to deteriorate their performance. what
do we do? So, it's a broader problem and
there are a lot there's a lot to say
about it, but one common pattern is the
separation between rules and knowledge.
Rules would be a small amount of data
that you're providing it that you're
kind of shoving down their throat.
You're saying this will be in your
agent. going to see this every single
time and they have to be succinct and
what they should do is they should
include links and references to guide
agentic search around where can it fetch
additional information and that is the
knowledge and I'll give an example from
Tesla's content. So hopefully many
people on this uh uh in this event uh
here or virtually know that Tesla has a
spec registry and we it's a a dependency
system for knowledge. you can publish
context into it in this form we call
tiles and then you can consume that down
to your uh to your consumers right to
your agents uh and it will adapt it to
the local agent and you can do it for
your context but we also pre-populated
the registry with over 10,000 specs or
context uh that uh that that helps
agents use open source libraries better.
We've analyzed those libraries, we've
iterated, we've evaluated and we created
those. So let's let's look a little bit
at what is the structure of those. Um in
first of all we define a knowledge base.
So well what is the knowledge that you
want? So you do that in this tessle.json
file. In our example there are
variations of it we'll touch uh to say
this is the information I want. In this
case I have a bunch of libraries. I want
to know how to use them. And then you'll
see that each one of those is fragmented
into pieces. So the agent doesn't need
to suck it all up right away. Especially
for some of these libraries, there's a
lot to say. You don't want to hog the
context window. So there's a bunch of
different files.
The second thing we would do is we will
put a little bit of knowledge or a
little bit of rules in the agents MD
file and we'll say here's a link to your
knowledge. Uh we actually it's a bit
longer over here but we also give a
little bit of instruction of uh what is
the structure of the knowledge you might
find to the agent but it's a very small
amount of context that is in the roles
and always loaded. And then if you click
that knowledgemd file, you will get a
markdown file that the agent can easily
find out which libraries do you have a
little bit of information about them and
where can it learn more and then down
the rabbit hole it can learn more. It
has an index file it explains about in
this case next.js and then it can in
that file find links to additional
information. So this is like a human
clicking links on a website
[clears throat] right you have a summary
thing you're expanding a section or
you're clicking through and it's very
effective. This is a good way to give
the agent uh a way to find the right
information. Lean into its agentic
search capabilities, but don't ask it to
sort of browse the web and just figure
it out.
So hopefully at this point you're
saying, well, show me some data. I
realized as I was building it that uh
this is a Jaring Maguire reference and
not everybody knows that. It might be
like a my age is starting to defer of
it. Like it does say show me the money
typically. Um so okay can we see some
data right I make this claim that this
is a good way and a good effective way
to to make the agents work. Let's see
some data. I'll show two examples of
this. First is uh thanks to the great
work that uh the team at Versell has
done on Nex.js. So Nex.js JS is a very
well uh wellused very popular JavaScript
framework that is maintained and built
today by the Verscell team and they
published as a thought leader in the AI
space uh a benchmark about that tries to
measure how well can agents use Nex.js
and they created about 50 different test
cases uh and uh they ran it through
different agents to see how well they
can address those. It's interesting, by
the way, immediately to see that even
though Nex.js is so popular and has so
much content, it's like the sweetheart
of the training data, right? It's well
doumented. It's an amazingly like clear
set of data. The top agents, the ones
that did the best, still only got a 42%
score in this benchmark. And so that's
already interesting and a bit sobering.
But it goes to show, okay, can we
improve this with context engineering?
and in general that if you measure this
now I bet you all the agents are now
working on optimizing it and so our
question was okay we've done this can we
optimize this with context can we test
our uh uh our our knowledge like these
tiles that we create do they actually
make it better and we ran this eval
because we already had the eval so we
just had to compare the two test cases
and we're happy to see that yes yes yes
we can with the knowledge the success
rate like for us it was about 40% % in
our uh uh test environment. Success rate
of using SJS on this benchmark, it
jumped up to 92% if we got that info.
This is if we got you know the very
thoroughly created piece of information.
But we also find for instance that a
smaller prompt midway that just guides
the agent to look at the things that you
care about. Uh in this case, some
linting and some build errors actually
also bumped up the process
substantially. So sometimes it's
knowledge and sometimes it's steering
around what is it to pay attention to.
This is great for next.js
[clears throat] but this was a very
thorough benchmark set that required a
lot of attention. We can't do that for
everything. But what you can do when you
evaluate your content or when you have
something that is uh you don't have the
sort of the bandwidth to create a deep
benchmark for is that you can use LLMs
to create evaluation data. And so we
took 270 random libraries and we asked
the LLM to create test exercises for
them, a scorecard to evaluate how well
they did on that test and then we ran it
through agents. The data I have here is
for cloud code. We saw similar data for
cursor and then eventually you ask an
LLM to judge the result with that
rubric. And indeed when we ran that we
saw that on average across those 270 we
bumped up the success rate from about
60% to about 81% uh in open source in
agents ability to consume open source
across these 270 libraries and we did
that with a little bit of a shortening
of the time. So the agents were a lot
more successful in a little bit less
time a little bit faster which was
really encouraging. So this was great
and this is again the validation part.
We also had you always find these bits
of information that you don't know how
to expect. uh some interesting
information about the age of a library.
And so this graph shows with the same
test the success rate of the agent. This
is cloud code across uh correlated to
the uh age of the libraries. The
libraries at the left are the oldest.
The libraries on the right are the
newest that this is release date just as
a simple measure. And it's interesting
to see how the libraries that are 5 to
10 years old, those are the ones that
the agents do the best with. And we've
seen this with other agents as well. Uh,
and the distance is substantial. And
that makes sense because very old
libraries, they might have they might
have confusing information on the web.
Uh, maybe they don't have as much web
representation if they're truly old. And
the very new libraries often times they
haven't accumulated enough information
on the web and some of their data is
actually after the training data. And
our theory was that with uh with the
tiles, we actually can flatten that
line, right? We because we gave them the
information, they have it, so they
should use it. And indeed, we've seen
that we elevate the result more broadly.
And this was useful because it matches
our kind of anecdotal experience that um
using this type of knowledge, using the
right context, sometimes just helps and
sometimes it turns it from it doesn't
work to it works.
Um I'll move on to multiplayer, but just
one thing to say is that in context
engineering is actually a lot more than
what I'm showing right now. And there
are many many different tools and one
notable one is the ability to use a sub
agent in claude and now a few other
agents to be able to give it its context
and focus it. So there's a lot more to
do here and it's a worthy domain to
invest in.
So with that let's talk from single
player talk about multiplayer. In
multiplayer, the question is in your
team, in your organization, what context
do you want to provide and when? What
are the ways in which you can share
context across the team? I'll talk about
three versions of this. The first and
kind of easiest most sort of uh direct
way to share context is to put stuff in
the repo. As we said, the project itself
is the base context for an agent. And so
if you check in an agent MD file,
anybody that uses that repository would
load it. It's the repo or the path
within the repo. This is great and you
should do it and it is a perfect fit for
things that are repo specific knowledge.
Right? This is documentation about how
this application behaves or things like
that. Awesome. Perfect place to do it.
Highly recommended. Uh where it slightly
falters is uh one is cross repository
information. your be best practices,
shared libraries and all those feels a
bit odd to check those into a
repository. Would you check them into
multiple repositories? You might want a
different solution. And the second is uh
and I'm picking a little bit on backlog
MD over here. You know, it's a great
framework. We had a great workshop
yesterday about it. Um and you can see
though that you know those who adopt
agents and lean into them, what you find
in the repos is you find many duplicate
files. You find your sort of Gemini MD
and cloud MD and agent MD and cursor
rules and you'll find skills. You'll
find GitHub stuff.
and and that's not awesome. Uh and it's
not that you have this many files that
is the problem, but rather that they are
duplicative. There's often content that
is very similar within each one of them.
So that's a challenge.
The second tool that you have to
accumulate and to provide shared context
amongst your team is to give agents
tools to gather context. uh most common
is of course browsing the web but also
things that are more focused like hey
use this to uh uh this MCP tool to be
able to go and fetch uh code from GitHub
repositories and load them. So this is
I'd say you know first of all super
useful for discovery and exploration
like you know you you don't know which
library you're going to use clearly you
don't have the context for that library
as you're exploring you should have
dynamic tools to go and fetch that. It's
also great for dynamic data like uh uh
production data about how your system
ran or you know something that is
constantly changing. So for those it is
amazing. Uh it is not great when there's
a high potential to get the wrong
answer. Versioning is a is a strong
example of that. If you're using a
version that's not the latest and your
agent went to the latest GitHub repo,
it's going to get the wrong information
to operate with. And for complex topics
where there's subtleties, you know,
authentication related topics or um just
sort of complex environments,
it's also highly inefficient for
repeatedly needed info. So let's say you
can go off and find the relevant commit
at the relevant repo and read the code.
If you need this information seven times
a day, you know, five days a week, why
like why wouldn't you sort of gather
that context one time, store it,
evaluate it and then optimize for that?
Which gets me to the third mode which is
today kind of the cutting edge and it's
the notion of curated context or curated
knowledge. What you would have seen is
over the last couple of months you've
seen a lot of progress from all the big
agents uh uh providing reusable context
frameworks. So they have you have you
saw claude skills you saw cursor team
rules you saw GitHub copilot spaces uh
and you know these are these are kind of
acknowledgements from these agent
companies to say well we don't want the
agent to reinvent it every time we
actually want to allow you to share
things and to share practices and that's
great I highly recommend these platforms
you should learn about your environment
for it they're great for cross
repository knowledge uh they're great
when you're using often times you start
seeing people use uh maybe like a you
have a security code review bot that
runs in your review surrounding, but
that same context, you also want it when
you're building locally and maybe when
you're assessing an incident with
another agent. So, it's great to have
not just crossdevelopment repo, but also
cross use case knowledge. Uh, and
because they're built natively, they
tend to be kind of nice and elegant in
terms of how they interact, you know,
clawed with its skills, cursor with its
rules, etc. Uh, they're a bit of an
overkill for single repo information.
Maybe that's not too bad. But really the
biggest challenge with them is that they
are single agent. Um and that kind of
begs the question of do we think long
term that knowledge and context should
be managed per agent, right? Do you
think in your organization, in your
practice, do you expect that you would
use one agent for your org over time?
And I think the answer to that is no.
Like I think just like any technologies,
technologies will be better at one thing
versus the other. They will move. they
will change. Companies are big. People
will have preferences
and that knowledge as a whole should be
something that is a core competency of
the knowledge that you have and it
should be adapted per agent but it
should be your asset that is broader. So
that's the approach we have at Tessle.
You've sort of seen a bit of this
already. We have the Tessle JSON and
when you install this knowledge then it
will it will adapt it to the relevant
agent. It will store it as a cursor role
or it would store it as a as an agent MD
or whatever that is. Uh and then also
once we download that knowledge, the
knowledge is there as files and so you
can use it in whatever way that you
want. We do provide tools to make it
easier and better to work with it. We
want it to be seamless, but you're not
locked in to you need to use those tools
if you want to use different tools to
consume it. So we think this is
important when we think about uh uh kind
of broader long-term context management
and development.
And in fact, we're doubling down on
this. And just as a slight plug here,
you know, we are expanding the registry
into a full-blown TESL uh agent
enablement platform uh that will help
you gather and and this type of
knowledge like the packages you've seen,
create and run evaluations for them,
distribute them so that every repository
gets its knowledge uh and then help you
optimize that over time. Uh so this is a
commercial product and if you're
interested in being uh being part of it,
uh come come talk to us, see us or email
us at contact.io. fail if you're online.
So that's a good segue for just the
closing points around ecosystem context.
And you know when I just sort of sang
the sort of the uh the praises of why
ecosystemwide context from the registry
is helpful and you should use it and
it'll help you today. But in the long
run you do have to wonder who should
create this type of open source context.
know we we come along to someone else's
library and we create these agent docs
for them and we track them and that you
know we do it today because it's helpful
today and we want to help but long-term
is that right
and I think the answer is no like I
think over time kind of open source
context is really an aspect of agent
experience and it is the creator's
responsibility if you are an open source
maintainer if you are a vendor it's your
responsibility to have a great developer
experience it's also your experience
your responsibility to have a great
agent experience. You know, it is it is
in your control. It is something that
you can choose where to invest and
context is your best tool for that.
Context is both your documentation and
your UX. You know, you need to think
about what is it that you say there. How
do you distribute that to your users?
You know, do you want this indeed to be
single agent or multi- aent? And eval
are your tests. They're your moment of
defining what is correct and what is not
correct. And so, you should invest in
those. You should define them. And you
should ask your users for feedback on
when they work and when they don't work.
And you're it's your responsibility, but
you're not alone. You know, you have us
to help with our technology with our
platform on it. You know, feel free to
talk to us. You have the amazing AI
native dev uh community that you should
tap and they will help you. And
together, I think we want to create this
successful methodologies and actual
context that will help us all consume
software together better. Uh and if we
achieve all of that then we'll help
we'll successfully put everything in the
right context. Thank you.
[music]
>> [music]